for
for for
there we
go all right good morning can you all
hear me
yes okay Mr Bass I don't know if I could
hear
you uh oh there you go okay good thank
you your honor okay great thank you all
right we are now in session on this uh
Zoom Hearing in case number CV 35-
24-10 63 it's entitled DPW Enterprises
LLC and Mountain Prime 2018 LLC versus
Jeremy bass and Dwayne Pike um I note U
Mr Stoddard is present by zoom on behalf
of the plaintiff and Mr Bass is present
by Zoom representing himself Mr Pike is
represented by Ken Nagi and there was a
notice of non opposition and so Mr Nei
had indicated he was not planning on
being present at this hearing today on
this motion to dismiss and just to
clarify for the record this hearing
today is on Mr bass's motion
to find it back here it was filed on
August 14th it's the motion to dismiss
and strike the summons and complaint he
filed a memorandum in support of that
and in his memorandum he also referenced
his
response that he
[Music]
filed same day to
the
complaint and I note that there is a
response in the motion for summary
judgment that was filed by
plff the memorandum supporting that
motion for summary judgment also uh
detailed the plaintiff's opposition to
this motion to dismiss and strike the
Summons of Complaint and so this matter
was set for hearing
today um we do have one other issue we
need to take up but I don't know if you
want to do that first um Mr Bass just
filed and I don't know if he received
that Mr stod but he just filed late last
night or right before close a
business a motion to an affidavit it
says to essentially asking to continue
your motion for summary judgment it had
originally been set for the 15th of
October and then it was uh re another an
amended motion or notice excuse me was
filed setting it for August October
22nd and so Mr Bass you are seeking an
extension of time Beyond a uh October
22nd is that correct yes just a a small
window uh
more all
right and so uh Mr Stoddard I don't know
whether uh Mr Bass contacted you to see
whether you would agree to that or
whether this is a motion that you
haven't seen
yet uh yeah I haven't seen the motion
that was filed with the court I did look
on the docket this morning um I received
a email from Mr Bass a cryptic email
last night about needing more time but
it didn't reference more time for what
whether that was for today's hearing uh
or any of the other motions and so um
I'm not sure you know what the basis is
uh in my view uh my client purchased
this property in March Mr Bass is living
there rentree um and so uh obviously
they are uh wanting to get this matter
taken care of sooner rather than later
so uh without having seen the motion uh
I can tell you my clients would oppose
any additional continuance uh that
summary judgement hearing has been moved
now twice all at Mr naggie um request
because he has had other conflicts um
and been nice enough to reach out to the
court and find additional hearing dates
um and so um out of professional
courtesy to him I've been happy to move
those hearings because they have not
been for a a extended period of time um
and he's been able to obtain alternative
dates from the court on a relatively
quick basis so um you know Mr Bass
obviously has gotten the benefit of
those extensions because uh I haven't
wanted to bifurcate the summary judgment
motion and and take up two dates on the
Court's calendar uh and have instead
sought to just move B so um again I
would oppose any continuance of the
summary judgment
motion all right and just to be clear
you referenced um motions that have been
filed by Mr Bass I just want to make it
clear for the record that
originally uh the first motion that was
filed was the motion for appointment of
C counsil which we dealt with at the
last
hearing
on I remember what day we were in court
it was early
September I'm not seeing my minutes
so there they are September 17 we dealt
with with that issue which I denied the
motion for appointment of co-counsel and
then the second motion filed by Mr Bass
was this motion to strike the summons
and complaint which we have set for
hearing today and then he also filed a
motion to amend the filings to include
verification as well as a notice of
verification uh Mr Nei indicated that he
had no objection to that particular
motion and I believe that you have also
filed Mr Stoddard uh a
a notice of non opposition to that
particular motion to add the
verification so that one has been
resolved the only um motion that Mr Bass
has filed now that remains unresolved is
this motion to dismiss and then we have
plaintiff motion for summary judgment I
think that um
defendant Dwayne Pike through his
attorney Ki has filed an opposition
filed a response to that motion for
summary judgement and we just don't have
a response yet from uh Mr Bass and that
is what I was your honor uh just asking
for uh another week to to finish uh my
response um and that's all I uh and I'm
not unsure why uh the motion I did send
it out to both parties uh to Mr Nei and
and Mr solder uh so uh not sure did you
email that or did you yes I emailed him
and then there's also copy that's being
uh sent in the mail as well so um I'm
sure why got thank you and I will note
for the record that Mr Pike is not
present on Zoom Mr Pike your attorney is
not present because he filed a notice of
non-objection to Mr bass's Motion in
regards to his motion to dismiss um
you're certainly welcome to be part of
the hearing to uh to listen to what is
going on but my understanding is that
your attorney filed uh on your behalf a
notice of non-objection to this
particular motion okay thank you very
much all right and so um we'll get to
that motion to continue in a moment in
regards to summary judgment let's take
up the motion to dismiss and strike the
summons and complaint and so Mr Bass
this is your motion so I'd be glad I
have reviewed um first of all
your three page motion to dismiss and
strike the summons and complaint as well
as
the a 15-page memorandum in support of
that motion with attachments I haven't
numbered the
attachments um there exhibits
a through e or F excuse
me and then in it you referenced your uh
response to the summons and complain
I've reviewed that and I have reviewed U
Mr Stoddard um your the portion of your
memorandum that's in reference to this
particular motion the second half of
your memorandum and so with that in mind
um Mr Bass I would be glad to hear
argument um I believe that uh
the the whole uh of it to be
that they're wanting to be a
a buyer in good faith uh for Value um
purchaser bonafied purchaser in good
faith for Value um
and uh there's plenty of evidence that
there was uh coion and uh that the the
uh sale wasn't uh uh above board and
that they're not a a Bonafide buyer
and and that's the uh basis for
dismissal
um
yeah all right so just I want to
clarify
um spreading my notes
here so it's a essentially
down to three issues first you're saying
that the non-judicial Foreclosure sale
was uh was undertaken in bad faith yes
second you're saying that there was
plenty of evidence of coercion in
regards to that sale yes and then second
you're saying that DPW Enterprises
mountain mountain Prime 2018 LLC were
not Bonafide buyers of the
res first of all where is is the plenty
of evidence in regards to coercion of
the sale and why should this court
consider the sale when that's not an
issue before the
court uh your honor the
uh in order for them to uh have
possession of the house and the title
they would have to be a purchaser in
good faith for Value uh under Idaho
section uh
4558 and which is what would give them
that's the uh give them the right to
proceed forward um the evidence that uh
uh the evidence that I have uh is in
audio and video form uh as well as uh
pictures uh it's not part of this record
it is not part of it uh that's part of
uh I thought motion to dismiss needs to
be supported by evidence or uh some sort
of affidavit or some sort of proof not
conclusory statement
yes your honor and I I Gathering that uh
that fact now uh this is the hearing on
your motion yes
um I
was I didn't understand that you weren't
supposed to that you had to give
everything out right now um I thought we
were supposed to bring more evidence as
we went how else could the plaintiff
respond to your motion if you don't
present what it is you're trying to
argue
I thought this was a uh a notice
pleading state so I didn't I thought we
were supposed to bring and this is why I
needed co-council um these little
details I understood Mr Bass but I have
plenty of people that appear in front of
me representing themselves they read
through the rules and they figure out
what they need to
do I am instructed by the Supreme Court
to treat you no differently than I treat
an attorney if you choose to represent
yourself oh although I tend to give a
lot more grace to self-represented
litigant I and
that's my response to the summary
judgment was uh is what I was I that's
where all the evidence I was bringing
was attached to and that's part of the
reason why I was asking for more time I
didn't
uh I didn't know that I needed to bring
more than uh just
I guess enough to uh create a Shadow of
Doubt or some uh to this part so not a
shadow doubt standards preponderance of
the evidence in the Civil
matter that's the standard of proof that
I look
at okay
um I I have the evidence here I mean I
could show it I just I didn't have it I
wasn't I was that's what I was
presenting for the
the uh for
the let me just take this through and
maybe I don't know if Mr starter if you
want to address this first but let me
just take it through what my concerns
were um your first allegation in your
memorandum is that Carrington Mortage
Mortgage
Services colluded and price fixed and
exhibited coercion
in the foreclosure in the non-judicial
Foreclosure Cale that was a conclusory
statement that you made there's nothing
in there you make a lot of statements
but none of which is considered
evidence and then you talked about how
they delayed the selling while you were
waiting for money to clear up in your
mother's probate um and you're saying
that it was uh they didn't comply they
sold it too soon but my understanding
from the facts as were stated in Mr
Stoddard's memorandum is over a year and
a half went by after the default before
they did the Foreclosure sale
they yes it was a year and a half uh
after they went into default uh we uh
under the doctrine of the uh the park
performance um I had already paid uh we
had already entered and started the uh
the transfer to me um I paid the taxes
as well as the uh the insurance that
would nor come out of escro hold on
let's let's make a difference here so
they told notified you you were in
default of your mortgage yes which means
you didn't pay that's um and I don't
know whether to my knowledge you didn't
pay during the court the entire year and
a half but you were making some sort of
arrangement with no time frame that
you've referenced to try to pay off the
mortgage and in the meantime while you
were in possession of the home you paid
taxes you paid house insurance as a they
at this point were not the owners of the
residents correct until the de until the
Foreclosure
sale
um I guess you in possession of the home
and you paid the taxes for living there
no and you paid the homeowners insurance
so that comes out of escrow and no uh I
wouldn't normally pay that and that so
they took care of that and so part of
tax yes they would pay the taxes
normally for so the whole length of the
uh mortgage they would pay the taxes
this wasn't money that you were out it
was just payment by your mortgage
service as in the due course of business
as mortgage companies do they pay your
taxes to make sure they're paid yes
before and so after the
Foreclosure um we uh when I highlighted
the issues that were there and I we
didn't go into foreclosure because I
didn't make payments we went into
foreclosure because I stopped and said
hey you guys were caught in the fraud
and we need to look at this we went into
forbearance for uh over uh almost two
years worth of time that they kept you
were disputing the original mortgage
correct because the uh even the
instrument that is being foreclosed on
isn't even the instrument that we were
operating under the instrument you made
payments on since 2009 yes correct well
not 2008 and I didn't know that so the
original one that I the original
instrument that I made uh payments under
was from 2008 they made uh they
reconveyed that and said it was paid off
in full and then uh without my knowledge
so it was it was um picked up somebody
else purchased your mortgage no another
financial company P purchased your
mortgage no uh no your honor uh they did
a transfer of of mortgage and uh and
so transfer purchase essentially the
same thing somebody paid your original
mortgage broker money to take over your
mortgage and then your money now went to
that new person correct uh yes it sort
of but your honor the way they did this
was in order to create this confusion
that uh made it where it looks like uh
so the way they structure this is so
that it it produces this effect of well
you just didn't pay your mortgage you
everything looks okay um it's
transferred normally when it's not um
but that's that's kind of besides the
point here because that's something I
have to deal with uh with the Bank of
America and not with with uh with these
guys
but uh but with the the Foreclosure
itself uh when I when we went into
foreclosure it wasn't because I didn't
stop paying I I said hey there's a
problem here because they were trying to
get me to sign uh commit mortgage fraud
with them by bribing me uh to sign uh
mortgage uh a new deed that was
backdated for 2012 and 2020 and I said
you filed suit on that matter isn't that
correct uh yes and that was dismissed uh
that was actually against I want to say
that was against DP DPW you eventually
hadn't brought in the right parties to
contest that issue it was uh it was
against uh the trustee uh to stop the
sale because I was again trying to find
uh a lawyer and couldn't find anything
uh and because this is a such a
complicated matter and uh such uh
detailed kind of thing that I do need
help so that's why I was my apologies
the other case in it was CV 352 24164 63
was you against Bank of America Michael
nle the trustee and Carrington Mortgage
Service yes yes your honor and that case
was dismissed dismissed because I I
failed to uh procedure wise uh hand to
do uh serve correctly um and so while I
was finding a lawyer I uh I we just it
was in pause so I just kept it uh in
pause right so um that was originally
filed um back
in December of
22 and then in November of 23 the court
sent out a notice of proposed dismissal
for inactivity yes because there had
been 90 days failure to serve the
complaint with 182 and no activity for
90 days failure to serve the complaint
within 182 days and then you didn't
respond to that and so was dismissed in
December 4th yes and that's because we
were uh because we were already in uh I
was going to pay off the house in order
to take that off the table so that I
could do the suit without having to
worry about my home being used as
leverage against me so I was going to
pay that off and that's why we entered
into an agreement uh with Caron mortgage
for me to pay it off and so so at that
point they went ahead and stopped making
payments to taxes and insurance and I
took over the payments as as the part of
the transfer to start so we already
started actually doing the transfer
because I I instead of the more instead
of the escrow paying for uh the
insurance and the taxes I started paying
it and uh they gave me the payoff uh
amount and uh as I was waiting for the
escrow and so they knew that that was
coming and on the and the whole reason
why we had the contract uh the lease
agreement that happened before was
because it was not expected for them to
just suddenly uh go against our
agreement of of me paying it off and
then they just went sold it let me
interrupt for a moment I'm sorry um I'm
not sure it has bearing on this case but
out of curiosity what was your agreed
deadline for you to pay from pay off
that amount that they said you could in
order to keep your home uh it was as
soon as the probate was off uh to be
finished and we had regular uh updates
every month uh to let them know where we
were in the probate as far as everything
goes and so Harrington mortgage said
don't worry we're going to just let this
extend out there until someday your
probate is taken care of is that what
you're is that what you're representing
no no not at all there was or was there
a deadline that they wanted you to have
that done they did not give me a
deadline
no I I at some point within that year
and a half they apparently decided not
to wait any longer longer for this
probate to
occur and and sent you notice of the
Foreclosure sale uh no they every month
they they uh they continue to uh to they
postponed it every month and because you
can only put it out for 30 days I guess
uh and so the probate was going to end
and we were just getting done with it
actually in
February uh and and they were going to
get paid off actually in
March this this is this they knew um but
uh what ended up happening was I they
called me on a Friday I didn't get the
call and then on Monday uh they went
ahead and uh it was or I think it was
Monday um where they went to go ahead
and and uh do we did the same normal
monthly cycle of I let the uh the the
other side the trustees know that we
were still uh doing the probate we're
still uh moving forward I just paid the
taxes I just paid the uh Insurance um
we're we're moving forward on everything
and uh but because I didn't call uh
because I didn't pick up their phone
call on uh the day before they went
ahead and pushed forward on on Friday
Friday because I didn't or that that
February uh because I didn't answer the
phone call uh and then when I called
back uh they
uh just got just decided to to push
forward despite the fact that we already
were moving forward in things they had
already sent me the payoff we were wait
we had to get a re uh re-updated number
so they were sending me new numbers uh
and and they were in process too um but
we had the numbers uh the initial
numbers to pay off and
uh yeah we we were already in process
and so why didn't you show up at the
auction and tender an offer that you
owed the 163 uh because that would have
been uh that would have been a crime if
I had done that I would have been
participating in a fixed auction which
uh which the representative that was at
the auction which was there was only one
bidder that was there uh that was the
same lady that had called me and tried
to intimidate me into selling to her
ahead of time and when I uh and I have
that that's part of the evidence that I
was going to give to the uh with in
response to the the uh
uh the dismissal or uh summary the
motion for summary judgment the evidence
that I was going to file with that uh is
the the video and uh of
of it and the conversation from the lady
that uh she called and said that they
had been talking with the bank and uh
setting the price uh they were setting
the prices and negotiating ahead of time
which is that's illegal in itself
because it's a it's a public auction uh
there's there was no biders uh there was
one person that came with printed checks
they didn't do any bidding um and if I
had participated it would have been in a
fixed knowingly fixed
uh auction that
would yeah uh if it's price fixed then I
would be participating in that uh that
but I was there at the auction say if
it's price fixed you're asserting it's
price fixed now you're saying if it was
price fixed you don't have evidence of
that do you no I do I I have uh them
admitting to it that they were price
fixing it and them would be
uh well let me get that up then uh her
name
is what company does she
represent uh the plaintiffs right now
DPW Enterprises and Mountain Prime 2018
LLC yes your
honor I'm grabbing uh her name right
now
see her name
is the apologies whatever the
representative her name is of the
plaintiff so what you're alleging then
in your motion to
dismiss is one bad PA bad faith for the
non-judicial Foreclosure sale from
Carrington uh Mortgage
Services you assert that there was
coercion you didn't say on behalf of
whom I assume that's
carington and that you said said that
that the current plaintiffs were not
Bonafide
buyers yes and for that reason you're
saying that I should dismiss this
eviction case yes they don't have rights
uh because the
the because they're not bonified buyers
and uh and the the sale needs to be
vacated and which is part of the filings
that I and you understand that the
vacate any request to vacate the sale is
beyond the scope of this case it's
beyond the uh
it's I understand it that is uh
Beyond I guess I I I I really don't
understand uh if it that it's I I'm not
allowed
to you're making accusations against
Carrington Mortgage Services they're not
a party to this case I'm making
accusations uh uh against the
buyers and how are they going to know
what went on throughout the course of
your negotiations if that's what they
were with Carrington Mortgage Services
for that year and a half following their
notice of foreclosure well default so uh
there's several reasons why they would
know uh one there is uh do they
represent Carrington Mortgage Services
no they represent themselves as the
buyers that were negotiating with cared
mortgage they're a separate entity yes
representing themselves a separate
entity represent the interests of
carington Mortgage Services no they were
they're separate entity representing
themselves uh in negotiations with
Carrington Mortgage so they were party
with cared mortgage not uh not as cared
mortgage so they were uh making bids
along with other developers with Caron
mortgage and they basically held an
auction uh in private and then came
themselves
uh to the just this came and and uh had
with printed checks and there was no
bidding at the auction there was at the
public auction That was supposed to be
there they had done this and settled it
before so no no other developer came to
bid uh there was no bidding at all uh at
the auction which is what I have video
and and audio of uh as well as the them
the representative that came to the
public auction she uh is the one that
contacted me before telling me that they
were price fixing it and that she was
cuz she didn't uh she she was trying to
scare me into selling it to her so that
way
uh it would be a better deal um so let
me just get this straight my
understanding is Carrington offered for
you to buy out your mortgage at
163,000 that didn't happen within a year
and a half they gave you notice and set
it for a trustees
sale at the sale it was purchased by the
plaintiffs in this matter and as I
understand it I thought I read this
somewhere but correct me if I'm wrong it
P it was purchased for 150,000 it was uh
yeah their initial uh so in other words
Carrington took a loss no no oh no you
you owed them 163 3,000 they took
150,000 on it no uh after 15 years
they've they have uh been paid almost
2,000 uh
$200,000 um and it wasn't car interest
tends to do yeah and and Caren and
mortgage uh they only came on to the uh
the whole of it in
2015 um and that's part of the reason
why they were trying to get me to commit
mortgage fraud by having uh a new deed
signed for
2012 with their name name on it and my
ex-wife's name on it in
2020 so it was backdated for
2012 and uh and so they were trying to
get me to sign these papers for a new
deed that was backdated uh because we
were because we were operate that's what
they were operating under so the deed
that we're uh that they're that's
foreclosing on right now that the
instrument that's on
record that is not even uh the terms or
anything that we were operating under so
that that one's uh is just there uh Bank
of America's already agreed that the the
uh the conveyance the reconveyance was
legit and that's part of the problem is
is that what we're operating under the
instrument that we operating on is not
what was
recorded now Carrington Mortgage had
sent to Ido State Department of Finance
a instrument that was not recorded
presents it as if it was recorded and
what we were operating under which it
does fit the terms that we were
operating under and that one's not and
so that's that was that was part of the
packet that I'm presenting uh that I was
that I'm asking for you know another
week to be able to finish but uh they
had sent me a whole another set of of
papers that we were operating under
that's what we went through uh that's
what we were uh they should have been
foreclosing on um because it had all the
correct numbers and everything like that
but as far as far as uh as far as uh the
payoff goes I only got the final payoff
that we were discussing in December so
it was only a matter of a month time
between uh getting that number of the
number for the payoff to to hand him a
check uh in order to take the house off
the the table uh that that was only a
month's time so they gave you the what
they just said you would have to do to
pay off the mortgage in December yes and
then in February they put it up for sale
the truste sale no uh no your honor um
they started for closure in in March of
the year before of
22 uh yes your honor and they gave you
the notice in uh December of
23 and then it went to the non-judicial
forclosure sale in February of
24 correct no no your honor um that is
not correct uh they gave me notice of of
foreclosure in 22 uh
we uh and it every month they kept going
to uh postponing it uh the the auction
at your request correct uh yes okay uh
well actually at First uh at the
first eight months of that was not at my
request they did it because of of
litigation and uh I was working with and
still am working with authorities right
now uh for this so I have uh with the
SE an open uh investigation and with the
lon police uh open investigation as far
as uh the criminal aspects of this uh so
they been open since 22 uh they notified
you of default no that came after uh the
the investigation started uh in
23 uh in roughly
uh oh no I'm sorry 20 uh in the
beginning of
uh actually it depends on which one on
which people uh part of the
investigation is so there's multiple
people M multiple entities that are have
open cases uh some of them have started
in 23 and some of them have started a
little later so the one with the Leon
Police uh is in
24 um the uh uh Department of or the
office of the com controller uh is in 23
i' Department Police Department
investigation began before or after the
sale uh began uh after the
sale did the investigation with the
other entity that you were referencing I
think you said the SEC did that begin
before or after the sale I believe the
one with the SEC began before the sale
um and the one with comp controller uh
for uh the treasury uh that one began
before the
sale uh just before uh the sale
right all right so as I understand it
you don't think that this was an
appropriate foreclosure sale you think
there was bad faith you think that there
was coercion that the current plaintiffs
in this eviction case are not Bonafide
buyers throughout through the trustees
sale that's why you're asking for this
petition for eviction to be
dismissed yes um and the evidence you
have presented me on your motion to
dismiss consists
of
nothing I understand that and that's uh
and
that's that's the packet that I'm giving
with with for evidence we'll do a
summary judgment later but on the motion
to dismiss you wanted it heard
separately from the summary judgment so
that's what we're doing yes sir H all
right so uh Mr
Stoddard thank you honor I think the
courts aware the standard on a motion to
dismiss is that all of the uh averments
of the non-moving party are accepted as
true uh with that in mind the court has
before it as part of the complaint a
copy of the issued trustees
deed uh it reflects that the property
was purchased by my clients for
$65,000 $165
34671 so the property was purchased at a
public
auction where my client was the highest
bidder paying an excess of what Mr Bass
owed on the loan uh per his own payoff
that he attached to his document
um there's been nothing presented in his
motion or supporting
documentations of any collusion coercion
fabricated fraudulent
documents uh again they are as Court
noted merely conclusory statements uh
what the record reflects is that there
was a
default uh notice was given under the uh
Ido trust Deeds act sale was set
postponed for an exceedingly long amount
of time I think partially due to Prior
litigation between Mr Bass and his and
the trustee and the lender uh and
ultimately a sale date set a sell
held uh Mr bass's comments even indicate
nobody was prohibited from going to that
sale apparently he went to it or
somebody did and filmed on his behalf if
no other biders show up besides my
client um you know that ends up being
lucky for my client um but there is
other otherwise no evidence that people
were were deceived or told there was no
sale the record has uh the copies of
those sale notices um and so because of
that if if Mr Bass has issues with his
prior lender his prior servitor the
prior truste he's certainly free uh to
pursue those claims with whatever
Authority he wants or or the court um
but the issue before the court today is
my clients right to and interest in that
property having purchased it at the
trustee sale for uh 100 you know over
$165,000 uh which was paid um and
because of that the motion to the Smith
I think fails um both because of lack of
evidence but because there has been a
proper claim pled with proper supporting
documents in the
record right thank you Mr stard
um in regards to this motion to dismiss
I'm going to take this matter under
advisement I'll issue a written decision
in due course um meanwhile we have the
plaintiff's motion for summary
judgment currently set for it's been
filed since middle of September but now
it's set for hearing on October 22nd it
was a continued hearing and Mr Bass you
filed the motion yesterday evening
asking for that motion for summary
judgment to be delayed at least a week
yes sir for two is that correct yes
Shon um Mr Stoddard I know that you it
was originally set for the 15th and it
was moved to the 22nd though I think
that was based on Mr nei's uh
availability who represents Mr Pike is
that
correct that is correct
Ron if I were to Grant a weak continence
to the 29th do we know whether Mr n is
available
did you your you don't know Mr shter I
do not I mean my my thought is is that
if the request for continuance is merely
to provide Mr Bass additional time to
prepare his opposition
materials um then I'm happy to
shorten uh my time frame so we can still
have the hearing on the
22nd
um well even if I granted the week so
that he 14 days prior to the hearing
that would need to happen today the
response um it didn't sound like Mr Bass
was ready to file that today no your
honor um I need a I need an additional
week to finish transcribing uh and to
finish uh the last of my uh papers uh
and together so you need to tell the
15th then to file your response
uh that would be yes your
honor and Mr Stoddard you're willing to
wave the time that rather than 14 days
you're willing to go with seven days
prior to the hearing for that response
to be filed that that's fine with me
your honor again I I think the issues
that of which Mr Bass was complaining um
are against parties other than my client
uh and then frankly belong in a a
separate unrelated suit so um you know
whatever he's going to present I I think
ultimately is not going to have any
bearing on my client's position which is
it purchase the property there's a trust
deed the statutory framework in Idaho
says the that fail final and uh we're a
good faith purchaser so um I don't mind
shortening it seven days because we can
get it heard on the 22nd which is
already clear with uh Mr Navy's calendar
and already the time set for hearing the
summary judgment against Mr Pike as well
right and
so assuming Mr Bass could file his
opposition materials and then email them
to me on the 15th I could likely have my
response uh filed by Friday the 18th and
then that would get the court um you
know Monday uh to review my response if
it hadn't already reviewed Mr Pike
material to that or Mr bass's materials
at that point but all right so if I so
Mr Bass guess I guess kind of um
splitting the baby in the middle here um
I will allow you to file your response
rather than have it due today um you can
file that a week from today on the 15th
and make sure that um Council Mr Nei and
Mr Stoddard get a copy of that email
that to them at the
eservice um addresses that are listed on
their pleadings thank you honor and then
um and then if you're going to have
reply to that Mr Stoddard um that would
be then due on the
11th and that would give the court time
to read everything on the 14 the 11 your
honor would be I'm sorry the 18th 18th
my apologies certainly
fine so then that would give me time to
uh review uh whatever is recently filed
on the 21st before we have hearing on
this on the 22nd to 10 perfect thank you
your honor all right um is there
anything else and I will have a decision
in regards to this motion to dismiss
prior to that hearing date on the
22nd okay anything else we need to take
up for
today I do not believe so your honor no
from your honor all right thank you then
we'll be in reset and I will see you all
on the 22nd of October thank you your
honor all right have your day you too
good day Jud evens you too Miss
Pike e
for
okay
today's 202
24108 it's
947 a.m. joury pass 31782 that was Court
yay